thejewelhut.co.uk 2013-05-07

# Privacy Statement The Jewel Hut

The Jewel Hut privacy policy outlines our commitment to protecting and respecting your privacy. We regularly review this policy to ensure the best possible service to customers. By visiting our website you are accepting and consenting to the views and practices described in this notice.

Controllers of Personal Information

Any personal information provided to or gathered by us is controlled by T. H. Baker and Co Ltd of 95 High Street, Brierley Hill, West Midlands, England, United Kingdom, DY5 3AU.

Collection and Use of Personal Information About Customers

When you place an order with us you will be asked to enter your name, address, email address and a contact phone number as well as a password. This will create a user account for you which will allow you to track the progress of your order and will enable you to make future purchases more easily. By submitting your personal data, you agree to the transfer and storing or processing of this information. By ticking the tick box to receive promotional e-mails, you agree to receive marketing communications from T. H. Baker and associated companies. We do not ask you for your payment card information at this point, so no financial information is stored in your user account.

The information we learn from customers when they place an order helps us personalise and forever improve your shopping experience with us. We use personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, to: handle orders; deliver products and services; process payments; contact you about orders, products, services, special offers and promotional activities; update our records; to improve our store and platform; prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website; and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf. Any third parties must use the information in accordance with this privacy notice and as permitted by the UK's Data Protection Act 1998.

Confidentiality

We will only release personal information when we feel it is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of thejewelhut.co.uk, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purpose of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, sharing or otherwise disclosing personal information about customers for commercial purposes.

Controlling Your Personal Information

You may choose to restrict the use of your personal information and opt out of receiving direct email marketing communications from us. When you are asked to provide information on the website, look for a tick box that you can tick or untick to indicate your preferences.

Alternatively, if you have already signed up to receive emails from The Jewel Hut, please note that you can unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time by clicking the link available in all outgoing e-mails. Otherwise, you can request to be removed from our mailing list by emailing sales@thejewelhut.co.uk, calling us on 01384 78431 or making the request in writing to the following address:

T. H. Baker / The Jewel Hut  
95 High Street  
Brierley Hill  
West Midlands  
DY5 3AU 

Please be assured that information about our customers is an important part in the running of our business and we will not sell on this information to other parties. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Cookies

Cookies are small software files generated by a Web server and stored in your computer, ready for future access. These files are contained in the HTML information which flows backwards and forwards between your computer or mobile device and the servers.

Cookies are used by The Jewel Hut to deliver the best possible shopping experience for customers. They help the website store important information, such as the session cookies that remember items placed in the shopping basket during browsing.

Our use of session/tracking and analytics cookies is unobtrusive and intended as a means of improving the experience of the website for consumers. Some parts of the website will run less efficiently if personal privacy settings block cookies. However, it is entirely within your rights to refuse to accept cookies; you can do this by activating the setting on your internet browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies.

Please note this website allows cookies from carefully selected third parties, including Google, to further enhance the shopping experience – for example, by enabling us to provide users with relevant advertising based on a user’s prior visits to the website.

For a more comprehensive overview of cookies and how to manage and/or them, please visit our Cookie Policy & Your Privacy page.
